I'm on a journey out to see
the world While I'm on my own,
I've yet to reach the end So won't
you come along with me right now?
Surely then we can!
Follow me now as we
journey on from sea to sea
For that treasure known
by everybody as one piece.
Even though they laugh and
say it's just a fantasy.
We are going, there's no doubt we go.
Cause we can feel the
rush of energy overcome.
It will lead the way.
Keep pretending that you know what to do.
Books will only get in the way.
No guides for today.
Do not worry soon.
The rain will be gone with the wind.
Keep your chin up, raise the anchor.
Now that's what you'll do.
Give it time and calm.
The storm that you have built within.
Come and have not forget number two.
Once tomorrow's wind picks up.
We set self cause we can't.
Fresh enough, stand tall.
And take a look at one of you.
All the journey makes
me want to see somebody.
There are things out there
you just won't believe.
Beyond your wildest dreams.
Don't think for a second.
It's not the truth.
That's the story.
Most will believe.
Not me.
Come and see.
I am on a journey.
Out to see the world.
Don't all on my own.
I've got my group of friends.
Together we've got our way.
That's how it's done.
Says your captain.
Who says it can't be done.
We haven't even tried.
Gotta just believe.
We'll make it to the end.
I just wanna do it all right now.
Together surely we can.
Yes, we can.
You can.
Just take this moment in.
We can.
I can.
Just take this feeling in.
Right now.
Oh yes, we can.
Yes, we can!
Those two are gonna find the mink tribe.
And when they do, they're
gonna ask about Raizo.
Then we're all super screwed!
Indeed.
The search for some samurai who
wasn't even here was devastating.
The Mokumo duktum was
destroyed as collateral damage.
Let's hurry.
It might not be too late.
Right, off we go then.
This is nothing to monkey around about!
That's the visitor's bell!
Samurai! Samurai! Samurai!
We'll head to the city.
Tell anyone who is capable to follow me.
Sir!
Duke Dogstorm, a warning is ready
to go with your command, sir.
Good.
That bell is rather cacophonous, isn't it?
Not to mention ceaseless.
I believe it is to announce
the arrival of a visitor.
They must be welcoming us to their land.
How reassuring.
But I confess, Sir Law's
words leave me uncertain.
The allegedly human-hating inhabitants
here are actually the minks?
Yes.
It's not that I doubt the
words of our associate,
but it just doesn't seem
to make any sense to me.
If that's what people say,
then I wonder what happened...
Hello, Father!
Good to see you!
Momonosuke!
Kanjuro, too!
We are reunited at long last!
Indeed.
So sorry to make you worry.
Are you not with Sir Luffy?
Why are you here all alone?
To be quite honest,
I have been ill at ease ever since
we first set foot upon this land.
So I have been sleeping in a
room apart from the others.
Poor thing.
I'm pained to hear it.
When I awoke moments ago, I was alone.
So I went searching to find the others.
Curious that the others are missing,
but it's likely they're simply
preparing a welcome for us.
That is doubtless the case.
Why do I have to run before breakfast?
I told you!
Cause Kin'emon and what's his name?
It's Kanjuro!
Right!
Kin'emon and Kanjuro are here!
The whole country's already in an uproar,
ringing the visitor's bell
and yelling about samurai!
To make matters worse,
Cat Viper is running to the city
with a team of guardians as we speak!
Think we'll get another feast?
Sure would be awesome
to do two days in a row!
I'm willing to fight!
Obviously!
And I can't blame them.
They were wrongly accused of hiding
a samurai and nearly died for it.
Where are the samurai?
We'll find them right away, sir.
People are coming here from all directions,
so they should catch them along the way.
Pedro!
What do you see?
This is bad.
Still haven't heard any
word about the samurai?
My men are on the hunt now.
Master, we have to pull back!
Why would I do that?
Hurry, please!
I don't see anything here.
Please, just keep walking.
They've noticed each other!
There's no escaping fate anymore!
Master, your grace.
It's not worth it, don't fight.
Please calm down, you're
both still injured.
Some manner of altercation.
It can't be?
oh man that was close crazy close!
you're in danger, don't say another
word and go back to the sunny quickly.
how many years has it been?
you gotta look like a wreck,
you're one to talk, mutt seems you're.
I'm missing one of your legs down there.
Somebody stop him quick!
Well, it's not gonna be me!
Where is Raizo?
Hand him over already.
I know you're hiding him somewhere.
Let me say it one more time.
There is no Raizo here!
Search through the country as
much as you, Karoo, please!
But you'll find no samurai!
I wonder if you'll say goodbye to this leg
first, or tell us where the samurai is.
I'm gonna keep hacking away
until you give me what I want.
So what's it gonna be, Dog King?
Give up Raizo, or give up your leg?
There's nothing I can do.
So take the damned leg if you got or must.
What can you gotta do with one hand?
You certainly can't defeat me.
Go back to your lasagna
and eat yourself to death.
Out with it!
Where is Race?
How the hell should I know?
Someone from the land of Wano
has no business in this country.
They can't even fight.
You gotta make sure of
that with your poison gas.
But you cowardly curse!
Crap, you don't think he's
gonna break the chains, do you?
Is the gas really working?
Immobilize his arms!
Better hurry, I'm breaking free!
My people are no threat to you,
Karoo, but I won't go down so easy!
No, Master, you'll die!
Wanna stab someone?
I'll take every last spear you've got!
Master!
I was so sad when I found out that
you gotta had lost one of your legs.
Cause I was hoping you gotta
would lose your life instead.
This land ain't got room for two kings.
You've said enough, please stop it.
Well we can get rid of one
now, since we're both here.
I've been waiting for this day. Huh?
A dog and a cat? Hey!
I heard those two were
strong, but this is scary.
Stop fighting now!
Oh, Greg, you ruined everything you don't!
It's true.
A summoner!
I hope you're happy now!
They're all gonna kill you!
Come on, run away!
Momo!
Release me from your missile!
Why do all of you have a death wish?
Momonosuke, wait!
Kanjino!
What are you doing?
You gotta get out of here! Run! Hurry!
Cat Viper!
Dubstorm, just listen to me!
They don't mean this
country any harm, I promise!
I am the Samurai Kin'emon, a
loyal retainer of the Kozuki clan.
hailing from the land of Wano.
I am here to reunite with my
comrade Raizo, a fellow warrior.
Can he be found in this land?
Look, he's not here!
The country was practically
destroyed because of it, you moron!
Do something.
On it.
Oh, I've longed for this day.
I swear on my honor,
I don't owe this Race.
If the man you're talking about is
here, then you can take my life!
So Raizo is here.
And he is well.
I'm glad to hear it.
Thank you, friend.
Hey, hold on, you two!
You're telling me Rhizo has
been here from the start,
and you all knew the whole country?!
But, but, you all nearly died and
nobody here said a single word!
This city stood for a thousand
years and now it's ruined!
I'm sorry, but we had to keep
it secret even from you, Karoo.
For many years, we have been like family
to the Kozuki clan from the land of Wano.
There's nothing that can't be rebuilt.
Our people would never sell out a friend.
Reports claim he attacked the Navy vessel
transporting Doe Flamingo
and was soundly defeated.
That's bullshit!
Hey! Sir!
Tell me, do I look dead to you?
Uh, no, not at all!
You look very alive!
Allow me to offer proof of our bond.
No mistake,
the crest of the Kozuki clan,
for I have seen it upon our
two kings and Race as well.
Kozuki.
Well, jeez, that didn't
go like we thought.
I was getting ready for a fight, but
it turns out they're best buddies.
Who knew?
It's no one's fault.
We may be allies, but some
secrets have to be kept.
Wow.
So the doggy and the kitty have
the same hidden crest as Kin'emon?
If the bond they share is that
strong, it must be quite the story.
Dogstorm.
Cat Viper. I'm surprised.
I wasn't certain I would find you
two alive and well, but here you are.
We kept the faith, although death would
have been a mercy after what happened.
Well, if we waited here, we knew
we'd see Yugara someday at least.
Kin'emon was talking
to me, not you, Karoo.
Try waiting your turn for once.
Huh?
Kin'emon was clearly getting
bored talking to you, Karoo.
And since he is our esteemed guest,
I thought it would be
considerate of me to take over.
They're not going to start
fighting again, are they?
That's what they do.
Why don't you, Karoo, take a catnap?
I'll sleep when I'm dead.
I can help with that. Yeah?
You want to go another round?
That's fine with me, you three-man.
That's enough! Stop! Both
of you! Stop fighting!
What has transpired to
make you hate each other?
So, in days past, you two used
to be the best of friends.
I, uh, I forbid you to ever fight again,
and if it's over my father,
then it makes it even worse!
You know how much it would break his
heart to say this—it's too cruel!
Lord
Odin would?
would
Momo?
He said it would break his father's heart
to see this, but Kitaman's right here,
isn't he?
Please forgive us.
Lord Momonosuke, you're absolutely right.
I'm ashamed of myself.
They both stopped!
I can't believe it.
Master is bowing his head.
That's who he is, I see.
I concur with what Lord Momonosuke says.
I must apologize for this deception.
As you may have surmised,
Lord Momonosuke is not my son.
In all honesty, the boy that you see
before you is the son of Lord Kozuki Oden.
great daimyo of Kuri in the land of Wano.
This means Dogstorm, Catviper,
Kanjido, and myself honor him as lord.
The Kozuki have an heir?
That's a huge secret!
So what?
Momo is a big shot?
There are kings among his retainers.
He might be a lord with substantial power
If our true identities were
revealed during our travels I feared
that it might attract the attention
of deadly enemies Therefore,
we pretended to be father
and son Forgive me,
it's not that I did not
trust you So much as I
struggled to find the right
time to reveal the truth
I really thought you were a family
They are quite alike, such naughty boys
forgive me for deceiving you in truth
i am a lord yes and a naughty one
i'm no such thing who cares not me i
didn't ask for your opinion now bow
down to me luffy it's me if you think
we're gonna worship you all of a
sudden you need to get yourself a
reality check here shrimp lord momonosuke
There we go again, yet we
owe our lives to Sir Luffy.
He is a pirate after all.
Of course he's brash.
And he keeps our lord occupied.
Luffy's a brute!
Oh, how he fixes me, Onami!
Poor thing. Oh.
Little brat, remove your
hand, lest I smite you. Hey.
By the way, Momo, if your
father is the Lord of Wano,
his castle must be full of treasure. Hey!
You're a really bad person, aren't you?
He faced that hardship only months ago.
Yes.
Their cheer is doing wonders.
It might just save him.
Let's make a truce.
If we keep dwelling on the past.
We'll just make the young lord suffer.
For his sake then.
I'll extend my hand as an ally.
But never as your friend!
and so it shall be.
My word!
They both made up? Really?
Unreal!
I can't believe it! It's a miracle!
The king of the day and the
king of the night shaking hands?
That's the power of the Kozuki clan!
We can climb the whale from here.
If you've got to learn which vines to
take, it's possible to reach the top.
And this is where Ryzo's hiding, right?
Nin-nin! Ninja!
Nin-nin!
It's a real-life ninja! Nin-nin!
He stalks the shadows! Nin-nin!
I'm starting to feel ill again, Kiyama.
Should I take you down?
Don't force yourself if you're truly sick.
It's just, the higher we go, the
louder the voice in my head gets.
Then be proud, your
father had the same power.
Indeed.
And he wasn't the only great man
who heard the voice. You're right.
In fact, I was thinking the same thing.
Wow!
A real-life secret passage!
Whoa!
On the tail of a whale!
Who'd have thunk it?
Even if someone did come up
here, the door is well hidden.
Follow me.
It's a long fall to
the bottom. Don't slip.
What was that noise?
Race, without a doubt.
He's so close! Ninja!
Ninja!
Oh!
Get out of here, ninja!
There he is.
Behold, Race, the great ninja.
Oh, boy!
You've come at last, Cap Viper.
Curse you!
Why didn't you hand me over to the
enemy and spare your countrymen?
Everyone who brought me
food was grievously injured.
My heart could scarcely take it.
I was told this land is safe now.
Is that true?
If it fell to ruin while I was
held here, I'll never forgive you!
Kaya!
That's not what ninjas are like at all!
Who goes there?
Are you invaders?
Tell the truth!
Why are you here?
It's Raizo!
Ah!
Kin'emon, Kansuro, Lord Momonosuke!
And you're all well!
Thankfully so.
Raizo!
You see that?
Huh?
It's the crest of the Kozuki clan.
Like Kinemon's tattoo.
The crest here has adorned this
secret passage for centuries.
And that stone, the deep red, I've
never seen one in such an odd color.
Yeah, that is a poneglyph.
We know all about your
history, Nico Robin.
I was told the people of
Ohara can read those words
So can you tell me what
makes this poneglyph unique?
None of the ones I've
encountered thus far were read.
But I don't understand the significance.
This one has a different purpose.
Perhaps you'd like to read it?
Yes, if you don't mind.
Be my guest!
Is something wrong?
You've all been glaring at me
ever since you walked in here.
Are you really a ninja?
What?
Are you questioning me?
Please excuse our friend's insolence.
Worry not.
The Straw Hat Pirates are fine allies.
They saved our lives.
Is that so?
If you're really a ninja, prove it.
Come on, throw a jerk in for me.
And meditate under a waterfall.
Say nin and do some ninja magic.
Oh, show us your Earth techniques first.
But you've got to do fire next.
And water, too!
You're asking too much of me.
Why do you pirates like ninjas so much?
It ain't because we're pirates, brother.
Huh?
Oooooooope! Super!
From the day they're born, every
man thinks ninjas are cool.
Oh, you guys are making me blush.
Hey, ever go out with a
kunoichi, a lady ninja?
Show us your jump training.
Leap over some bamboo shoots.
You can do the shadow
clone technique, can't you?
Do the thing where you hide in the
ceiling and get stabbed by a spear.
Summon a giant frog and ride on his back.
Hold a scroll in your mouth and
say nin nin while you make pose it.
No, that's enough.
Stop imposing your
ninja stereotypes on me!
Ninjas don't say Ni-Nin.
All of these ideas of yours are fantasy.
You bear, you got a
weird body and no moves.
How are you a ninja?
It's true.
This physique of mine doesn't make
me terribly popular with Kunoichi.
Hey, rude! Dude!
Listen up.
A true ninja master has a
quiet but resolute heart.
One who lives in the shadows does
not put his techniques on display.
Ninjutsu is not a mere party trick.
Meatball!
Huh?
Smoke escaped to Higgs! Nyah!
He disappeared!
Huh?
I didn't disappear at all!
Why I'm right here?
Whoa, that's wild!
And here, too. And here.
Oh, it's me.
This is my shadow phone technique.
That's awesome.
You dare question my prowess?
Flower shuriken.
Shinobu.
Shinobu!
Invisible to the ladies,
invincible in battle!
Rise all of the mist has arrived!
Ha!
All for free!
With the story we got here!